<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Join Top-notch Innovative Team - Ventory on Ventory | #1 Solution for Inventory Control</title>
    <link>https://ventoryapp.github.io/careers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Join Top-notch Innovative Team - Ventory on Ventory | #1 Solution for Inventory Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Ventory</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ventoryapp.github.io/careers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Full Stack Engineer Team Lead</title>
      <link>https://ventoryapp.github.io/careers/full-stack-engineer-team-lead/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ventoryapp.github.io/careers/full-stack-engineer-team-lead/</guid>
      <description>Full Stack Engineer Team Lead - Belgium Job Description Ventory is currently looking for a Full Stack Engineering Team Lead to join its Engineering Team.
Our Engineering team is looking for an experienced Typescript developer that has a strong affinity for Operational focus in deploying, automating and developing the strategic product roadmap.
Our development stack consists of React, Typescript (node.js) and Dart (flutter). As we are a mobile focused solution the Flutter stack is important but languages can be learned on the job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sales Development Representative (SDR) Europe</title>
      <link>https://ventoryapp.github.io/careers/sales-development-representative/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ventoryapp.github.io/careers/sales-development-representative/</guid>
      <description>Sales Development Representative (SDR) Europe - Belgium based Job Description Ventory is currently looking for a Sales Development Representative (SDR) to join our growing sales team. As an SDR, you will play a crucial role in generating new business opportunities by identifying, contacting, and qualifying potential customers.
An SDR at Ventory is the first point of contact for many of our customers. You’ll be responsible for strategically prospecting and qualifying leads that will grow our business and drive us towards our revenue goals.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
