<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ventory | #1 Solution for Inventory Control</title>
    <link>https://www.ventory.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ventory | #1 Solution for Inventory Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Ventory</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 12:22:22 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ventory.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Enterprise Sales Account Manager (Europe)</title>
      <link>https://www.ventory.io/careers/enterprise-sales-eu/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 12:22:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ventory.io/careers/enterprise-sales-eu/</guid>
      <description>Job Description At Ventory, we are reimagining the Supply Chain industry and the way field stocking locations and critical components are managed. Through its technology platform, Ventory enables enterprises to connect, digitize and control their remote field inventory. Thus, helping them reduce wastage, increase service levels while also help improving their cashflows.
Ventory is currently looking for an Enterprise Sales Manager Europe to join its team. In this role you will be responsible to help Ventory gain even more exposure across Europe by doing sales on existing and new enterprise customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Application</title>
      <link>https://www.ventory.io/careers/open-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 12:22:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ventory.io/careers/open-application/</guid>
      <description>Job Description At Ventory, we are revolutionizing how enterprises digitize their supply chains. Our platform enables organizations across multiple industries (Life Sciences &amp;amp; Healthcare, Humanitarian Relief, Solar &amp;amp; Renewables) digitize their field inventory.
About You: You are passionate about technology. You love learning and can quickly adapt. You have an affinity towards addressing challenges with innovative solutions, enjoy working with and growing together with a team, and want to play a pivotal role in the success of a young company making an impact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sales Development Representative (Europe) </title>
      <link>https://www.ventory.io/careers/sdr-eu/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 12:22:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ventory.io/careers/sdr-eu/</guid>
      <description>Job Description At Ventory, we are reimagining the Supply Chain industry and the way field stocking locations and critical components are managed. Through its technology platform, Ventory enables enterprises to connect, digitize and control their remote field inventory. Thus, helping them reduce wastage, increase service levels while also help improving their cashflows.
Ventory today has global partnerships with accounts such as Microsoft, Zebra, Oracle, DHL among others and customers that trust our solution in &amp;gt;20 countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sales Development Representative (US) </title>
      <link>https://www.ventory.io/careers/sdr-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 12:22:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ventory.io/careers/sdr-us/</guid>
      <description>Job Description At Ventory, we are reimagining the Supply Chain industry and the way field stocking locations and critical components are managed. Through its technology platform, Ventory enables enterprises to connect, digitize and control their remote field inventory. Thus, helping them reduce wastage, increase service levels while also help improving their cashflows.
Ventory today has global partnerships with accounts such as Microsoft, Zebra, Oracle, DHL among others and customers that trust our solution in &amp;gt;20 countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Full Stack Engineer</title>
      <link>https://www.ventory.io/careers/senior-fullstack-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 12:22:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ventory.io/careers/senior-fullstack-engineer/</guid>
      <description>Job Description At Ventory, we are reimagining the Supply Chain industry and the way field stocking locations and critical components are managed. Through its technology platform, Ventory enables enterprises to connect, digitize and control their remote field inventory. Thus, helping them reduce wastage, increase service levels while also help improving their cashflows.
Ventory is currently looking for a Senior Full Stack Engineer. Our development team is looking for an experienced Typescript developer that has a strong affinity for Operational focus in deploying, automating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License agreement</title>
      <link>https://www.ventory.io/legal/license-agreement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ventory.io/legal/license-agreement/</guid>
      <description>Please read this License Agreement carefully before using, accessing, downloading, installing or otherwise operating any of the Products.
By using, accessing, downloading or otherwise operating any of the products, Licensee constitutes an unconditional agreement to be bound by this License Agreement.
IF YOU DO NOT ACCEPT THE TERMS OF THIS LICENSE AGREEMENT, YOU ARE PROHIBITED FROM USING ANY OF THE PRODUCTS.
1. DEFINITIONS Agreement means this License Agreement and all schedules, appendixes and related documentations provided to Licensee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://www.ventory.io/legal/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ventory.io/legal/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>As the provider of the website https://app.ventory.io/, https://ventory.io (hereinafter “Website”) and a mobile application on the Apple and Google Play store, we at Ventory (“Ventory”) are Controller as defined in applicable data protection law, more specifically the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (“GDPR”), and are therefore responsible for the personal data (“Personal Data”) of the Website user. As a user of the Website you consent to Ventory use of your Personal Data under this privacy policy and you acknowledge and accept that Ventory processes your Personal Data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Use</title>
      <link>https://www.ventory.io/legal/terms-of-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ventory.io/legal/terms-of-use/</guid>
      <description>By using the website, platform and application services provided by Ventory you agree to the following terms and conditions:
  All information, content and analytic data and services provided under your registered user account on app.ventory.io (“User Account”), including the related graphics and other analytical information (“Information”), are for informative purpose only and considered to be confidential.
  The User Account is owned and licensed by Ventory to you for your own use only.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
