<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Real-time Smart Inventory Management System - Ventory on Ventory | #1 Solution for Inventory Control</title>
    <link>https://ventory.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Real-time Smart Inventory Management System - Ventory on Ventory | #1 Solution for Inventory Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Ventory</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ventory.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Full Stack Engineer Team Lead</title>
      <link>https://ventory.io/careers/full-stack-engineer-team-lead/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ventory.io/careers/full-stack-engineer-team-lead/</guid>
      <description>Full Stack Engineer Team Lead - Belgium Job Description Ventory is currently looking for a Full Stack Engineering Team Lead to join its Engineering Team.
Our Engineering team is looking for an experienced Typescript developer that has a strong affinity for Operational focus in deploying, automating and developing the strategic product roadmap.
Our development stack consists of React, Typescript (node.js) and Dart (flutter). As we are a mobile focused solution the Flutter stack is important but languages can be learned on the job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sales Development Representative (SDR) Europe</title>
      <link>https://ventory.io/careers/sales-development-representative/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ventory.io/careers/sales-development-representative/</guid>
      <description>Sales Development Representative (SDR) Europe - Belgium based Job Description Ventory is currently looking for a Sales Development Representative (SDR) to join our growing sales team. As an SDR, you will play a crucial role in generating new business opportunities by identifying, contacting, and qualifying potential customers.
An SDR at Ventory is the first point of contact for many of our customers. You’ll be responsible for strategically prospecting and qualifying leads that will grow our business and drive us towards our revenue goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Inventory Management for First Location - Ventory</title>
      <link>https://ventory.io/pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ventory.io/pricing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License agreement</title>
      <link>https://ventory.io/legal/license-agreement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ventory.io/legal/license-agreement/</guid>
      <description>Please read this License Agreement carefully before using, accessing, downloading, installing or otherwise operating any of the Products.
By using, accessing, downloading or otherwise operating any of the products, Licensee constitutes an unconditional agreement to be bound by this License Agreement.
IF YOU DO NOT ACCEPT THE TERMS OF THIS LICENSE AGREEMENT, YOU ARE PROHIBITED FROM USING ANY OF THE PRODUCTS.
1. DEFINITIONS Agreement means this License Agreement and all schedules, appendixes and related documentations provided to Licensee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://ventory.io/legal/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ventory.io/legal/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>As the provider of the website https://app.ventory.io/, https://ventory.io (hereinafter “Website”) and a mobile application on the Apple and Google Play store, we at Ventory (“Ventory”) are Controller as defined in applicable data protection law, more specifically the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (“GDPR”), and are therefore responsible for the personal data (“Personal Data”) of the Website user. As a user of the Website you consent to Ventory use of your Personal Data under this privacy policy and you acknowledge and accept that Ventory processes your Personal Data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Use</title>
      <link>https://ventory.io/legal/terms-of-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ventory.io/legal/terms-of-use/</guid>
      <description>By using the website, platform and application services provided by Ventory you agree to the following terms and conditions:
  All information, content and analytic data and services provided under your registered user account on app.ventory.io (“User Account”), including the related graphics and other analytical information (“Information”), are for informative purpose only and considered to be confidential.
  The User Account is owned and licensed by Ventory to you for your own use only.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
